Little Bear Sae-chan
Ready... start!
（純一）用意　スタート！
What a bear y situation...
（紗江）クマったなあ
あッ　と　冬眠前のクマさんは
A-As a bear about to go into hibernation,
I-I have to make sure I eat my fill before then.
お　おなかいっぱいに
しておかないと
ダメなんです　ごめんなさい
Sorry, but I'll have to eat you up.
だから　あなたを食べちゃいます
Rawr!
がお～ッ
あッ　ダメですよ
今ごろ死んだふりしても
It's too late to play dead now.
はい　カーット！
Okay, cut!
The first love that blossomed last Christmas between a boy afraid of love and a shy girl...
〈去年のクリスマスに生まれた〉
〈恋に臆病な少年と
内気な少女との初恋は…〉
How is it, director?
監督　どうでした？
うん　よかったよ
It's good!
Though, maybe you could make it seem more like you're just about to hibernate.
でも　もう少し　冬眠前って感じ
出してもいいかなあ
そうですね
私もそう思いました
You're right. I was thinking the same thing.
じゃあ　もう一度やってみよう
は　はい！
Okay, let's do it again.
O-Okay!
...seems to be growing ever stronger even after ten months had passed.
〈どうやら
あれから１０ヵ月たった今も〉
〈すくすくと成長しているようだ〉
出逢った瞬間
Deatta shunkan
From the moment we met
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
感じてた運命を 確信に変えたくて
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
SS
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
SS
＋
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
今日も 君の傍に居るのかな
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
君の全てに
Kimi no subete ni
Everything about you
Check My Soul
ハートが動き出した
Haato ga ugokidashita
My heart begins to wake
今君と一緒に駆け出そう
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Let's break into a run together right now
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
夢のような空間の中でも
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
Even in dreamlike moments
真実だけを見つめていたい
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
I only want to gaze at the truth
瞳の奥の
Hitomi no oku no
Inside your eyes
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Nakata Sae
1st Half
Doubt
Nakata Sae
1st Half
Doubt
Nakata Sae
1st Half
Doubt
The cafeteria ladies used to look like vending machines to her, but they're normal cafeteria ladies to her now.
〈以前は自販機だった
食堂のおばさん達も〉
〈すっかり
普通のおばさんになった〉
いらっしゃい
こんにちは
Welcome.
Good afternoon.
今日のおすすめは何ですか？
What's the recommendation for today?
ミートソーススパゲティかな
Meat sauce spaghetti, I suppose.
じゃあ　それにしようかな
I'll have that, then.
Make sure you eat your veggies.
野菜も食べないとダメよ
はい
Okay.
Eat your fill!
〈誰とでも　こんなふうに自然な
会話ができるようにもなり…〉
She's now able to converse with anyone naturally...
...and she's even become friends with
the puppy she used to be so scared of.
〈あんなに怖がっていた
こいぬとも仲良くなった〉
よし　よし…
すっかり仲良しになったんだね
There, there...
He really likes you now.
Yes, we even got a dog at my house recently, too.
はい　最近　ウチでも
イヌを飼い始めたんですよ
へえ
I see.
There, there.
よしよし
Seeing the girl mature like that made the boy as happy as if it had happened to him.
〈そんな少女の成長ぶりが〉
〈自分のことのようにうれしい
少年であった〉
大きいイヌは
やっぱり　まだダメです
I'm still really scared of big dogs.
〈やっぱり
僕がついていないとなあ〉
"She still needs me by her side, after all."
...was what the boy was thinking.
〈と　少年は思っているのだった〉
Here you go!
お待たせしました
An ube Mont Blanc cake and a café au lait.
紫芋のモンブランと
カフェオレです
ありがとう
ごゆっくりどうぞ
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
Could I please have some water?
≪（客）すみません　お水ください
はーい　ただ今　お持ちします
Yes, I'll be right back with it.
（美也）久しぶりに来てみたけど
It's been so long since I visited, but
Sae-chan sure is popular here as well.
ここでも　紗江ちゃんは
人気者だね
Here as well?
ここでもって？
Maybe you haven't noticed, Nii-nii, but her
popularity at school is also going through the roof.
にぃには
気づいてないかもしれないけど
学校での人気も　にょろにょろって
うなぎ登りなんだよ
へえ　そうなのか？
もう　お気楽だね
Wow, really?
You say it like it's nothing.
I mean, didn't you and Sae-chan participate in the
Best Couple contest at the Founder's Festival last year?
ほら　去年　にぃにと紗江ちゃん
創設祭のベストカップル
コンテストに出たじゃない
Y-Yeah.
あッ　ああ
Sae-chan was so pretty and adorable!
≪（美也）あのときの紗江ちゃん
きれいで　かわいかったもん
≪（美也）あれが　きっかけで
今じゃ　同級生は　もちろん→
Because of that, she's become really popular among her classmates, underclassmen and upperclassmen!
上級生にも下級生にも
モテモテなんだよ
それだけじゃないんだよ
And that's not all!
クラスの
創設祭実行委員に選ばれたんだよ
Her class chose her to represent them in the Founder's Festival committee!
そうなんだ
I see.
Sae-chan wasn't too happy about it at first because she thought it'd be a lot of work.
紗江ちゃん
最初は嫌がってたんだよね
忙しくなるし
結構　大変なお仕事だからって
But I reassured her, saying, "you'll be fine! You can do it!"
でも　美也が　大丈夫だよ
できるよって励ましたんだよね
I see. Maybe it's about time...
そうか　また僕の…
いや　教官の出番ってことになるな
...for me to play the instructor again.
〈そのとき　少年の頭の中では〉
Right now, the nostalgic sound of the girl
calling the boy "instructor" echoed in his head.
〈少女が自分のことを
「教官」と呼ぶ〉
〈あの懐かしい声が響いていた〉
≪（美也）にぃに
何変な顔してんの？
Nii-nii, what's with the weird look on your face?
N-Nothing!
別に！
Sae-chan's popularity will go up again for sure.
きっと　また　紗江ちゃんの人気
あがるんだろうなあ
どうぞ
どうも
Here you go.
Ah, thanks.
（生徒Ａ）ほら　あの子だろ
（生徒Ｂ）ああ　去年のベストカップルの
Look, isn't that her?
Yeah, she was in the Best Couple contest.
（生徒Ａ）そうそう　かわいいよなあ
ふふん
Yeah. She's so cute!
ごめん　待たせちゃったかな
Sorry. Did you wait long?
先輩　いえ　全然
Senpai!
No, not at all.
Like his sister had said, the girl
was now the center of attention.
〈妹の言葉どおり
今や少女は注目の的だった〉
The boy was proud that his girlfriend was so popular, but...
〈少年は　自分の彼女の人気に
鼻が高かったのだが…〉
≪（生徒Ｃ）隣の男　誰だ？
≪（生徒Ｄ）まさか　彼氏？
Who's the guy next to her?
Her boyfriend?
No frickin' way.
≪（生徒Ｅ）いや　ないでしょ
≪（生徒Ｆ）全然　似合ってないし
They totally don't match anyway.
What's with this difference in treatment?
〈なんなんだ　この差は…〉
Harsh reality tormented the boy.
〈厳しい現実に
少年は打ちのめされていた〉
Senpai.
先輩　今日は何食べますか？
What are you having today?
Uh, um...
ああッと　えーッと
あッ　今日のおすすめは…
Ah, today's recommendation is omelette rice.
This is bad. Really bad.
〈まずいぞ　まずい〉
Um... you don't like omelette rice?
あれ　オムライス嫌いですか？
No, that's not it...
いや　そうじゃなくて
紗江ちゃん　ちょっと待ってて
Sae-chan, wait for me a bit.
えッ？　ええ？　先輩？
Huh?
Um... Senpai?
I have to prove it to everyone.
〈みんなに証明しなくちゃ〉
〈紗江ちゃんの食べたいものを
ちゃんと選んであげて〉
I'll choose exactly what Sae-chan
wants to eat and escort her flawlessly.
〈完璧にエスコートすることで〉
I'll show everyone that I'm Sae-chan's boyfriend!
〈僕が紗江ちゃんの彼氏だって
ことを見せつけるんだ！〉
Food Coupons
今日は　僕に任せてくれないか？
は　はい
Wanna let me decide today?
O-Okay.
I'll leave it to you, then.
じゃあ　お願いします
Omelette Rice (Brown Sauce)
Omelette Rice (White Sauce)
What should I order?
〈何を頼めばいいかな？〉
〈うーん　え～ッと…〉
Hmm...
〈そうだ　さっき　オムライスが
どうのとか言ってたよな〉
I know!
She was saying something about omelette rice before...
《あれ　オムライス嫌いですか？》
Um... you don't like omelette rice?
よし！
All right!
〈どっちだ！？〉
Which one?
Which sauce does Sae-chan like?
〈紗江ちゃんの好みは
どっちのソースだ？〉
Omelette Rice (White Sauce)
Omelette Rice (Brown Sauce)
〈いつも　どっちを食べてたっけ〉
Which does she usually eat?
Um, I love beef stew.
《あの　私　ビーフシチューが
大好きなんです》
…の場合はブラウンソースだ
That's the case for brown sauce.
《ふふ…　クリームシチュー
おいしいですね》
This cream stew's delicious, isn't it?
…の場合は　ホワイトソースだ！
That's the case for white sauce.
Omelette Rice (White Sauce)
Omelette Rice (Brown Sauce)
〈うう…　どっちだ？〉
Which is it?
No!
〈いかん！　いつもいつも
紗江ちゃんの顔ばかり見ていて〉
I'm always looking at Sae-chan's face,
so I can't remember which one she likes!
〈どっちが好きだったか
思い出せない〉
〈ううう…〉
≪（薫）えい！→
ちょっと純一　早くしなさいよ
Come on, Junichi, hurry up!
こんなに並んじゃってるわよ
あッ…
Look at the line behind you.
（生徒Ｇ）おっせーな
（生徒Ｈ）早くしろよ
What's the holdup?
Just pick something already!
He's still not done yet?
私は　ブラウンソース派よ
て　薫はそうかもしれないけど…
I'm a fan of brown sauce.
That's the case for you, but...
大丈夫　うちの食堂のオムライスは
両方ともおいしいから
It's fine.
Our cafeteria's omelette rice is really good no matter which sauce you go with.
はずれはないわよ！
You can't go wrong!
お願いします！
Please!
Omelette Rice
(Brown Sauce)
(White Sauce)
Omelette Rice
(Brown Sauce)
(White Sauce)
Omelette Rice
(Brown Sauce)
(White Sauce)
Omelette Rice
(Brown Sauce)
(White Sauce)
Omelette Rice
(Brown Sauce)
(White Sauce)
Omelette Rice
(Brown Sauce)
(White Sauce)
Omelette Rice
(Brown Sauce)
(White Sauce)
Omelette Rice
(Brown Sauce)
(White Sauce)
Omelette Rice
(Brown Sauce)
(White Sauce)
≪（食堂のおばさん）はーい→
Okay! Brown sauce omelette rice
and white sauce omelette rice, right?
オムライスのブラウンソースとホワイトソースね
はい
Yes.
Afraid of failure, the boy decided to play it safe.
〈失敗を恐れた少年は
保険をかけていた〉
野菜も食べないとダメよ
Make sure you eat your veggies.
じゃあ　ミニサラダを
ドレッシングは…
I'll have a mini salad, then.
As for the dressing...
〈うわッ　ど　どれだ？〉
Wasabi Sauce
Thousand Island
Italian
Japanese
Sesame
Wh-What should I get?
What dressing does Sae-chan like?
〈紗江ちゃんの好みの
ドレッシングは…〉
Excuse me!
（梨穂子）すみませーん
和風ドレッシングお願いします
Could I have the Japanese dressing?
Here you go.
（食堂のおばさん）はい
R-Rihoko, why did you choose that?
り　梨穂子　なぜ　それを選ぶ？
何？　いきなり
Huh? Why the question?
いいから教えろよ
Whatever, just tell me!
Th-That's because, well...
そ　それは　その…
カロリーが一番低いからだよ
It has the least calories.
もう言わせないでよ～
Don't make me say that again!
そういうことか
I see.
だとすれば…
In that case...
体重を
気にしそうにない人は　どれだ？
What would someone who doesn't care about her weight go for?
What? That's mean, Junichi!
え～ッ　ひどいよ　純一！
Just tell me!
教えてくれよ
う～ん　好みもあるよ
Everyone has their own tastes.
（食堂のおばさん）はい　サウザンアイランド
Here. Thousand island sauce.
えッ？
That fluffy-looking girl always chooses this sauce.
それ　あのフカフカちゃんの分なら
いっつも　これだよ
あ　あの…　どうして
分かったんですか？
Um... how'd you know that was for Sae-chan?
紗江ちゃんのって
だって　あんたとフカフカちゃん
You and the fluffy-looking girl
always have lunch together, right?
いっつも一緒に
仲良くご飯食べてるでしょ
あッ　ああ
I guess some people really do know.
〈分かる人には　分かるんだよなあ〉
〈いやあ　よかった　よかった〉
Man, I'm so glad!
〈いや　食堂のおばさんに
分かってもらえてることは〉
Well, I dunno if you should be
glad that a cafeteria lady knows.
〈喜ぶべきことなのだろうか〉
先輩　あの　大丈夫ですか？
えッ？
Senpai, um... are you doing okay?
あの　やっぱり　私が運びますね
Um... I'll carry the food instead.
Sae-chan?
紗江ちゃん？
Senpai, leave it to me.
先輩　任せてください
私　バイトで慣れてますから
I'm used to it from my job.
どうぞ
Go ahead.
Ah, I'll go buy some drinks.
あッ　飲み物　買ってきます
う　うん
O-Okay.
お待たせしました
Here you go.
Here, I got you bitter melon soda.
はい　先輩には　ゴーヤソーダ
You like it, don't you?
これ　好きでしたよね？
うん　ありがとう
Yeah, thanks.
〈少年は思っていた
少女にくらべて　自分は〉
The boy was thinking that, unlike the girl, he
didn't really know very much about his girlfriend.
〈彼女のことを　よく分かって
いないのではないかと…〉
But it's not too late.
〈でも　まだ遅くはない〉
〈早速　少年は　心の中のメモ帳に〉
The boy had already allocated a page in the
memo pad in his head for what the girl likes.
〈少女の好きなものの
ページを作ったのである〉
紗江ちゃん　それ好きだよね
はい
Sae-chan, you like that drink, right?
Yes.
〈そして　その１ページ目に〉
And on the very first page, he noted that the girl likes panda cocoa.
〈少女は　パンダココアが大好きだ
と書いたのであった〉
A few days later, the boy and girl went to a shrine.
〈それから　数日後のこと〉
〈少年と少女は
とある神社に来ていた〉
〈それは　少女の
たっての希望だったのだが…〉
This was something the girl had really wanted to do.
But why did you want to come here?
でも　何で　ここに来たかったの？
お願いごとがかなうって
雑誌に載っていたので
It said on a magazine that this place really does grant wishes.
へえ
I see.
紗江ちゃん
はい
Sae-chan.
Yes?
何　お願いしたの？
えッ　そ　それは…
What did you wish for?
U-Um...
秘密です
えッ　秘密って…
It's a secret.
A secret?
ご　ごめんなさい
S-Sorry.
I can't tell you.
先輩には言えないです
The boy really wanted to know what the girl's wish was,
〈少年は
少女のお願いごとが何なのか〉
〈すごく気になっていたのだが〉
but he felt a barrier from her refusal
to tell him and didn't press any further.
〈少女の聞かないでバリアを感じ〉
〈それ以上
踏み込めないのであった〉
Clouds of insecurity arose gloomily in the boy's heart.
〈少年の心に　不安という雲が
モヤモヤと浮かんだのである〉
Squirrel Sae-chan
Penguin Sa
Honey Sae-chan
Cat Sae-chan
Seal Sae-chan
"She does such adorable things! I should know more about her than anyone else."
〈こんなかわいいしぐさをする
少女のことは〉
〈自分が誰よりも
知り尽くしているはずなんだ〉
That's what the boy was telling himself.
〈少年は　自分に
そう言い聞かせていた〉
≪（美也）にぃに　大変だよ！
美也　いきなり入ってくるなよ！
Nii-nii, this is bad!
Miya, don't just barge in without warning!
みゃー　大事なことを忘れてたよ
I forgot something really important!
Sae-chan's apparently having a marriage meetup today!
紗江ちゃん
今日　お見合いするらしいよ
ええッ！
〈紗江ちゃん　僕には　そんなこと
ひと言も言わなかった〉
Sae-chan didn't mention anything about it to me.
Senpai, I'm sorry.
《〈先輩　ごめんなさい　神様
私達を別れさせてください〉》
God, please break us up.
そ　そんな　まさか
あのときの　お願いって…
C-Could that be what she was wishing for?
〈ぼう然自失の少年であった〉
The boy was in a state of shock.
紗江ちゃんのおウチは
お金持ちだから
Sae-chan's family is really wealthy, so I'm
sure her parents are deciding her marriage.
きっと　親同士が決めた結婚だよ
M-M-Marriage?!
け　け　結婚！？
〈妹の火に油を注ぐ発言は
さらに少年を狼狽させた〉
His sister's words, akin to pouring more oil onto the fire, panicked the boy even more.
ああ　愛のない結婚を
させられちゃうなんて
I feel so bad for Sae-chan for having to marry someone she doesn't love!
紗江ちゃん　かわいそうだよ
もしかして　相手は悪の組織かも
Her partner might come from a criminal organization...
紗江ちゃん
どうなっちゃうのかな…
What'll happen to Sae-chan?
ど　どうしよう…
Wh-What should I do?
Anyway, I'll go see Sae-chan before the
meetup and find out exactly what's going on!
とにかく　お見合いをする前に
紗江ちゃんに会って
どういうことか確かめなくちゃ！
美也　場所を教えてくれ
Miya, tell me where she is.
にぃに　紗江ちゃんを
悪の手から救い出すんだね
Nii-nii, you're saving Sae-chan from the hands of evil?
みゃーも手伝う！
I'll help!
All right.
よし！　そうだ
Oh yeah.
行くぞ！
Let's go!
〈少年よ　そのビデオを
持っていく必要はあるのか？〉
Hey, boy. Was there really a need to bring that videotape with you?
≪（美也）うわ～ッ
おっきいホテルだね
Wow, this hotel's huge.
う～ん　これじゃあ　紗江ちゃんが
どこにいるか分かんないよ
There's no way we can figure out where Sae-chan is.
ああ
Yeah.
I wonder who her partner is.
≪（美也）それにしても　相手って
どんな人なんだろうね
《にっしっしっしっ
もはや　まな板の上の鯉》
You're just like a fish on the chopping board!
《覚悟は　い～い？》
Are you ready?
S-Senpai! Help!
《しぇ　しぇんぱ～い　助けて～》
助けに行くよ　紗江ちゃん！
I'll save you, Sae-chan!
にぃに？
Nii-nii?
Miya, we have to find Sae-chan and stop the meetup no matter what!
美也　なんとしても
紗江ちゃんを見つけて
お見合いは阻止する！
R-Roger!
ラ　ラジャー！
≪（司会）ウエディングケーキ
入刀です
And the wedding cake is cut!
うわーーーッ！
うわ～ッ！
Nii-nii, are you okay?
にぃに　大丈夫？
急がないと…
We must hurry!
Where's Sae-chan?
紗江ちゃん　どこにいるんだ？
早く見つけてとめなきゃ
I have to find her and stop her!
にぃに　あそこ！
Nii-nii, over there!
紗江ちゃん…
Sae-chan...
にぃに？
ダメだ…
Nii-nii?
It's no good...
Go! Now!
行って！　早く～
ちょ　おい…
Wait, hey!
いいから早く　行って！
Whatever, just hurry up and go!
クソッ
Damn it!
Th-This meetup is over!
そ　そのお見合い
ちょっと待ったー！
Oh, no...
あっちゃ～
Senpai?
先輩？
イヌのお見合いだったんだ
A meetup for your dogs?
はい　いとこの家の
エリカちゃんと…
Yes, for Erica-chan from my cousin's house...
あッ　イヌの名前です
Oh, that's the dog's name.
ウチのサトシくんと
お見合いさせることになって
She's meeting Satoshi-kun from my house...
But Miya said...
でも　美也が…
Um, I'm pretty sure I told Miya-chan the same thing...
美也ちゃんにも
そう言ったはずなんですけど…
Right...
〈少年には　妹が早とちりをする
様子が手に取るように分かった〉
The boy could already see how his sister
had quickly jumped to the wrong conclusion.
Hey, Miya-chan.
《あのね　美也ちゃん
今度の日曜日ね》
My puppy's having a meetup this coming Sunday.
《ウチのワンちゃん
お見合いするんだよ》
《ふ～ん》
《じゃあ　またね》
See you.
《バイバーイ》
Bye-bye!
《あれ　そういえば　さっき》
Wait, I get the feeling Sae-chan
just told me something incredible...
《ものすごい言葉を
紗江ちゃんから聞いたような…》
Hmm... What was it?
《う～んと　何だっけなあ…》
《あッ　紗江ちゃんが
お見合いとか言ってた！？》
Sae-chan was talking about a meetup?!
Meetup
This is bad, Nii-nii!
《大変だよ　にぃに！》
She's seriously unbelievable...
まったく　あいつは…
あの　先輩
さっきのビデオって…
Um, Senpai?
The videotape from just now...
ああ　あれは　その…
お見合い相手に
Oh, I brought it here so I could show your partner just how much I think about you,
僕が　どれほど紗江ちゃんのことを
思ってるかってことを
分かってもらおうと思って
一応　持ってきたんだ
since I didn't think my words would be very convincing...
なんか言葉だけだと
説得力ないから…
〈苦しい言い訳
しかも　メチャクチャである〉
That's a pretty terrible excuse.
What's worse, it doesn't even make sense.
そうだったんですか
I see.
ああ　でも　必要なかったね
うん
Yeah.
But it looks like I didn't need it.
Yes.
紗江ちゃん　その着物
すごく似合っているね
Sae-chan, you look really good in your kimono.
そ　そうですか？
あッ　ああ
R-Really?
Y-Yeah.
ちょうどよかったです
せっかく着たので
Good thing I wore it.
After going through the trouble of putting it on, I actually really wanted you to see it.
本当は先輩に見てほしい
って思ってましたから
き　きれいだね
I-It's pretty.
あ　ありがとうございます
Th-Thank you.
〈少年も少女も　本当に言いたい
ことを胸に秘めているのだが〉
The boy and the girl are hiding what they want to say in their hearts.
Man, these two really test your patience.
〈何とも
じれったい２人なのである〉
あッ　あの…
何？
U-Um...
What?
I'm really happy that you came running for me.
先輩が　こんなふうに
駆けつけてきてくれて
私　うれしいです
I really panicked.
僕　焦っちゃったよ
本当に　紗江ちゃんが
ほかの人とお見合いしちゃって
If you really were meeting up with someone else...
もしかして
結婚なんてしちゃったら
If you really did end up marrying him...
どうしようかなって思って…
I didn't know what I'd do...
Seriously.
まったく…　美也が親同士の決めた
政略結婚みたいなこと言うから
It's all because Miya made it sound like some political marriage decided by your parents.
I wouldn't do that with anyone else.
ほかの人とはしないです
えッ？
結婚はしないです
I won't marry... anyone else.
ほかの人とは…
私　お願いしましたから
I made a wish.
ずっと先輩と
一緒にいられますようにって
I wished that I could be with you forever.
あッ　もしかして　この前行った
神社でのお願いごとって…
Wait, are you talking about the wish you made at the shrine we went to?
はい　お願いごとを人に話すと
Yes.
I heard that your wish won't come true if you told someone about it...
かなわないって聞いてたから
だから　秘密って言ったの？
は　はい
That's why you kept it a secret?
Y-Yes.
紗江ちゃん
Sae-chan.
先輩…
Senpai...
Yup, yup.
≪（美也）うんうん
They've really come to like each other.
すっかり仲良しに
なったんだね
よしよし
There, there!
（梅原）冷静に考えれば
分かるだろう
You'd know if you'd just calmly thought about it.
There's no way a highschool student would have a marriage meetup.
いくら何でも高校生が
お見合いなんてないだろう
まあ　今から思えば
そうなんだけどな
That's true, now that I think about it.
でも　よかったじゃないか
誤解が解けて→
But it's all good, right?
The misunderstanding's been solved and the
bonds between you two have grown even stronger.
また２人の絆が
一層深まったってことなんだろ
I guess that's true.
そういうことになるかな…
≪（梅原）ああ～あ　大将はいいなあ
絆があって
Man, you're so lucky to have bonds, boss!
俺には　まだ運命の赤い糸の先が
どこにあるのかさえ
As for me, I don't even know where my red string of destiny links to.
分かってないっていうのに
もう切れてしまっているのかも…
Maybe it's even been cut...
（詞）橘くん　お客様よ
Tachibana-kun, you have a guest.
確か　あの子　創設祭の…
I believe she's in the Founder's Festival committee...
うん
Yeah.
どうした？
What is it?
You know, Onii-chan, Sae-chan's in big trouble!
あのね　お兄ちゃん
紗江ちゃん　大変なんだよ
I don't know if I can trust your definition of "big trouble".
美也の大変は
当てにならないからなあ
今度は　ホントだよ！　ねッ？
It's for real this time!
Right?
S-Senpai...
しぇ…　先輩…
紗江ちゃん？
Sae-chan?
Sae-chan was chosen as the
Founder's Festival committee president!
紗江ちゃんね　創設祭の
実行委員長に選ばれたんだよ
すごいでしょ！
えッ　どうして紗江ちゃんが？
Isn't she amazing?!
How'd that happen?
もうッ　言ったでしょ
Geez, didn't I tell you?
紗江ちゃんは　今や
輝日東のアイドルなんだからって
Sae-chan's pretty much the idol of Kibitou these days.
What should I do, Senpai?
どうしたらいいんですか？　先輩…
The boy was thinking that nobody other than him could help the girl face the challenges to come.
〈このとき　少年は思った〉
〈次なる試練を迎えようとする
少女の力になれるのは〉
〈やはり　自分をおいて
ほかにはないと〉
せっかくだから　やったほうが
いいんじゃないかな
It's a good opportunity, so you should go for it, I guess.
ほええ…
Ahh...
See? I told you my brother would say that.
ほら　お兄ちゃんも
そう言うって言ったでしょ
ねッ　やろうよ　紗江ちゃん
Come on, you should do it, Sae-chan.
僕も手伝うから
I'll help too.
せ　先輩や美也ちゃんが
そう言うなら…
S-Since both of you say I should...
私　やります
I'll do it.
よっし！　決まりだね
が　頑張ります
All right! It's decided, then.
I-I'll try my best.
Well said, Sae-chan!
よく言った　紗江ちゃん！
All right, we'll do some training to
make you a great committee president!
よし　立派な実行委員長になる
特訓をしよう！
Yes, i-instructor!
はい　きょ　教官！
ああ　またそう呼んでくれ
Yeah, start calling me that again!
〈久々に　少女の口から
「教官」という言葉を聞いて〉
The boy's heart burned with enthusiasm upon
hearing the girl call him "instructor" after so long.
〈少年の心は熱くなっていた〉
〈とはいえ　２人の前途には〉
Though, the events that lie ahead
of them would surely test their love.
〈その愛を試される出来事が
待ち受けているのであった〉
〈少年よ　少女よ　大丈夫なのか？〉
Hey, boy and girl.
Will you both be okay?
朝を運ぶバイクの音が
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
僕に時間の流れ告げ
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
もうどこへも行けない気持ち
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
君に渡す覚悟決めた
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
未来に散りばめた 予定は隣に 君がいてほしい
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
息を吸って吐き出す
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
言葉は幾度もため息に変わるけど
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
伝えたい言葉はただひとつだけ
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
好きだよ
Suki da yo
"I love you"
僕の告白
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
Next episode preview.
Thank you so much, instructor.
It's been so long since you called me that.
教官　お疲れさまでした
Y-Yes.
久々に
そう呼んでくれるんだね
Ah, I have an idea.
は　はい
ちょっと思いついたぞ
Lemme look for it...
Sae-chan, could you try reading these?
サラサラサラっと
Yes. Um...
紗江ちゃん　これ
読んでみてくれないか？
"Master Tachibana"?
Yup.
はい　えっと…
「橘師匠」
"Tachibana the Great".
Yup, yup!
「橘名人」「橘社長」
"President Tachibana", "King Tachibana",
"Tachibana the Expert"...
「橘王」「橘熟練者」
Yup, yup, yup!
"Champion Tachibana"!
Next Episode
Nakata Sae
2nd Half
Wish
Next Episode
Nakata Sae
2nd Half
Wish
Next Episode
Nakata Sae
2nd Half
うん　うん　うん！
「チャンピオン橘」
Next episode: "Wish"!
うおーーーッ！